{"data":[{"question":"Mai and Lan have a row because they have misunderstood one another.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"have","b":"because","c":"misunderstood","d":"one another","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- One another-> each other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The workers are building a new bridge which is 150 meters in high.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"building","b":"a new bridge","c":"which","d":"high","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- High-> height","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"It's no use asking them keep quiet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"no use","b":"asking","c":"them","d":"keep","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Keep-> to keep","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"This text is too long for me to read it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"long","c":"to read","d":"it","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- It-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't get used to doing so difficult exercises.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can't","b":"used","c":"doing","d":"so","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"My father doesn't know speak English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"My","b":"doesn't","c":"speak","d":"English","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Speak->how to speak","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She behaves as if she was a baby.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"behaves","b":"as if","c":"was","d":"a","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"You wanted me to tell you about what I was doing here and how was my life.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to tell","b":"about","c":"was doing","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Was my wife -> my wife was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The course is good, but more hard than I thought.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"but","c":"more hard","d":"thought","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- More hard-> harder","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Sleeping all day, to eat too much and never going out is unhealthy.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Sleeping","b":"to eat","c":"much","d":"never","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To eat-> to eat","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}